http://www.topcoins.com/privacy-policy.html

Our Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy was created to let you know what happens to
information supplied to us directly or indirectly through our contacts. Any
personal information collected by us is not sold or transmitted or used
in any way expect to continue to supply you with our information.
Personally
identifiable information, including credit card information, address,
date of birth etc which may be used with a credit authorization
we do
not want nor store this information which you may have supplied to the
payment processor.Some information that cannot identify any
individual, including cookies and web beacon page-tracking data, which
computer operating system is used, which browser and version is used to
access the site, etc. may be collected to help us provide a better
search environment for future viewing.If you register to
receive our Ezine or other modules requiring an email be returned to you
we will keep these files as secure as possible as they may contain your
email address, first name, photographs or other such data supplied to
us.
Home PageSite MapCoin BlogAncient CoinsBullion CoinsCoin TermsCollector SuppliesAmerican CoinsAustralian CoinsCanadian CoinsEuropean CoinsDetermining valueWorld CoinsCoin JewelleryCurrencyContact UsLinksOur StorePrivacy PolicyCoins n Kids
On Site Links for:Index, Home Page,Contact Us, Links, Privacy Policy, Site Map, Our Store,
Enjoy this page?
Please pay it forward. Here's how...
Privacy Policy, Home Page, Our Store,
© Copyright 1968
All Rights Reserved
by www.topcoins.com
No Reproduction Permitted Without Permission
